Guide to the Consumer Reports. Audiovisual materials, 1940-2011 and undated RL.11802
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Consumer Reports Television, 1967-2011; undated; 3
  - Consumer Education, 1967-2011; undated; 10
    - The American Consumer With Consumer Reports, Undated (Box 84, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0489)
    - The Dollars & Cents Show, 1982 Nov. 15 (Box 86, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-168)
    - The Dollars and Sense Show, 1982 Oct. 13 (Box 16, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-013)
    - The Good Buy Show, 1980 (Box 16, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-007)
    - The Good Buy Show, 1980 (Box 16, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-009)
    - The Good Buy Show, 1980 (Box 42, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-095)
    - The Good Buy Show, 1980 Sept. 17 (Box 86, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-176)
    - The Good Buy Show #14, 1980 (Box 43, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-117)
    - The Good buy Show #6, 1980 (Box 42, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-086)
    - The Good Buy Show #7, 1980 (Box 36, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-073)
    - The Good Buy Show #8, 1980 (Box 43, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-114)
    - The Good Buy Show #9, 1980 (Box 45, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-103)
    - The Holiday Show, 1985 June 21 (Box 15, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-021)
    - The Holiday Special, 1985 June 21 (Box 86, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-174)
    - The Shop Around Show, 1981 Sept. 10 (Box 86, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-172)
    - The Six Billion $ Sell, 1976 (Box 56, Film-reel RL11802-F16-164)
    - The Six Billion $$$ Sell, 1976 (Box 33, Film-reel RL11802-F16-127)
    - The Six Billion $$$ Sell, 1976 (Box 40, Film-reel RL11802-F16-141)
    - The Six Billion $$$ Sell, 1976 (Box 40, Film-reel RL11802-F16-142)
    - The Six Billion $$$ Sell Part 1, 1976 (Box 33, Film-reel RL11802-F16-129)
    - The Six Billion Dollars Sell, 1976 (Box 60, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0053)
    - The Smart Buy Show, 1982 Feb. 01 (Box 40, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-082)
    - The Smart Buy Show, 1982 Feb. 01 (Box 86, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-171)
    - The Smart Buy Show, 1982 Jan. 27 (Box 46, Video-reel RL11802-vid1-029)
    - The Smart Shopper Show, 1983 Jan. 18 (Box 37, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-066)
    - The Smart Shopper Show, 1983 Jan. 18 (Box 86, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-179)
    - Unsafe at any Price: a Consumer Reports Special, 1985 June 19 (Box 64, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-115)
    - Unsafe at Any Price: A Consumer Reports Special, 1985 June 19 (Box 37, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-057)
    - Unsafe at Any Price: A Consumer Reports Special, 1985 June 19 (Box 28, Video-reel RL11802-vid1-001)
    - Your Dollar's Worth, 1967 (Box 3, Film-reel RL11802-F16-041)
  - CRTV News, 1989-2003; undated; 11
    - Big Screen TV; Camcorders, 2000 Mar.; 2000 Nov. (Box 106b, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-261)
    - Demo Reel (Gilbride End), 1989 Apr. 14 (Box 36, Video-reel RL11802-vid1-016)
    - Feature Promo Tape, Undated (Box 87, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-180)
    - Feed 002, 1989 Dec. 14 (Box 42, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-096)
    - Feed 003, 1990 Jan. 18 (Box 15, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-029)
    - Feed 004, 1990 Feb. 13 (Box 43, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-112)
    - Feed 006, 1990 Apr. 19 (Box 43, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-116)
    - Feed 009, 1990 July (Box 36, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-076)
    - Feed 014, 1990 Dec. (Box 15, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-026)
    - Feed 017, 1991 Mar. 21 (Box 36, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-078)
    - Feed 018, 1991 Apr. 18 (Box 37, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-055)
    - Feed 019, 1991 May 16 (Box 15, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-027)
    - Feed 020, 1991 June 20 (Box 37, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-068)
    - Feed 021, 1991 July 18 (Box 44, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-077)
    - Feed 022, 1991 Aug. 15 (Box 45, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-107)
    - Feed 023, 1991 Sept. 12 (Box 44, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-079)
    - Feed 024, 1991 Oct. 17 (Box 37, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-056)
    - Feed 026, 1991 Dec. 19 (Box 26, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-018)
    - Feed 027, 1992 Jan. 16 (Box 44, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-076)
    - Feed 028, 1992 Feb. 13 (Box 38, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-058)
    - Feed 029, 1992 Mar. 19 (Box 44, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-084)
    - Feed 030, 1992 Apr. 16 (Box 26, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-021)
    - Feed 031, 1992 May 14 (Box 38, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-059)
    - Feed 032, 1992 June 18 (Box 38, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-057)
    - Feed 033, 1992 July 16 (Box 44, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-081)
    - Feed 034, 1992 Aug. 13 (Box 44, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-083)
    - Feed 035, 1992 Sept. (Box 44, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-078)
    - Feed 036, 1992 Oct. 22 (Box 44, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-074)
    - Feed 036 October, 1992 (Box 85, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0375)
    - Feed 037, 1992 Nov. 19 (Box 19, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-027)
    - Feed 038, 1992 Dec. 17 (Box 35, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-056)
    - Feed 040, 1993 Feb. 18 (Box 36, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-063)
    - Feed 041, 1993 Mar. 18 (Box 44, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-082)
    - Feed 042, 1993 Apr. 15 (Box 44, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-073)
    - Feed 044, 1993 May 15 (Box 26, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-020)
    - Feed 045, 1993 July 13 (Box 26, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-019)
    - Feed 046, 1983 Aug. 11 (Box 42, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-094)
    - Feed 050, 1993 Dec. 14 (Box 45, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-071)
    - Feed 051, 1994 Jan. 18 (Box 19, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-029)
    - Feed 053, 1994 Mar. 15 (Box 64, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-113)
    - Feed 054, 1994 Apr. 19 (Box 44, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-075)
    - Feed 055, 1994 May 17 (Box 64, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-112)
    - Feed 056, 1994 June 14 (Box 46, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-072)
    - Feed 057, 1994 July 12 (Box 19, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-026)
    - Feed 058, 1994 Aug. 09 (Box 45, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-069)
    - Feed 059, 1994 Sept. 13 (Box 44, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-080)
    - Feed 060, 1994 Oct. 11 (Box 19, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-031)
    - Feed 061, 1994 Nov. 15 (Box 45, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-067)
    - Feed 062, 1994 Dec. 13 (Box 64, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-114)
    - Feed 063, 1995 Jan. 17 (Box 45, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-068)
    - Feed 064, 1995 Feb. 14 (Box 45, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-065)
    - Feed 065, 1995 Mar. 14 (Box 45, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-066)
    - Feed 067, 1995 May 11 (Box 38, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-060)
    - Feed 073, 1995 Nov. 14 (Box 19, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-024)
    - Feed 074, 1995 Dec. 12 (Box 38, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-061)
    - Feed 076, 1996 Feb. 13 (Box 19, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-033)
    - Feed 077, 1996 Mar. 12 (Box 19, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-025)
    - Feed 079, 1996 May 14 (Box 26, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-022)
    - Feed 08, 1990 June 14 (Box 16, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-004)
    - Feed 093, 1997 July 15 (Box 19, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-039)
    - Feed 095, 1997 Sept. 16 (Box 19, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-038)
    - Feed 097, 1997 Nov. 11 (Box 19, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-035)
    - Feed 098, 1997 Dec. 16 (Box 26, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-023)
    - Feed 099, 1998 Jan. 13 (Box 45, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-070)
    - Feed 103, 1998 May 12 (Box 19, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-037)
    - Feed 104, 1998 June 16 (Box 19, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-030)
    - Feed 11, 1990 Sept. 13 (Box 16, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-002)
    - Feed 110, 1998 Dec. 05 (Box 19, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-028)
    - Feed 116 dub, 1999 June 15 (Box 26, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-017)
    - Feed 12, 1990 Oct. 18 (Box 39, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-047)
    - Feed 124, 2000 Feb. 10 (Box 19, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-036)
    - Feed 13, 1990 Nov. 15 (Box 64, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-140)
    - Feed 132, 2000 Oct. 05 (Box 19, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-034)
    - Feed 15, 1991 Jan. 24 (Box 38, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-052)
    - Feed 150, 2002 Apr. 04 (Box 19, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-032)
    - Feed 39, 1993 Jan. 14 (Box 16, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-001)
    - Feed 43, 1993 May 18 (Box 16, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-006)
    - Presentation Tape, 1995 Aug. (Box 84, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-125)
    - Presentation Tape, 1998 (Box 84, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0505)
    - Sales Demo #4, 1990 Apr. (Box 87, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-181)
    - Sample Tapes, Undated (Box 82, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0176)
    - 1996 Jan. 16 (Box 85, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0374)
    - 2000 Sept. 11 (Box 82, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0179)
    - 2002 Jan. 03 (Box 82, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0180)
    - 2003 Dec. 04 (Box 84, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0508)
  - Food and Health, 1980-2006; undated; 12
    - Consumer Reports Films The Food Show #12 R1, Undated (Box 9, Film-reel RL11802-F16-004)
    - Consumer Reports Films the Food Show #12 R2, Undated (Box 9, Film-reel RL11802-F16-005)
    - Consumer Reports Films The Food Show FB 21 - #30 R1, Undated (Box 8, Film-reel RL11802-F16-001)
    - Consumer Reports Films The Food Show FB 21 - #30 R2, Undated (Box 8, Film-reel RL11802-F16-002)
    - Consumer Reports Medical Guide.org B-Roll No bug, 2005 May 11 (Box 108, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-210)
    - Consumer Reports Medical Guide.Org B-Roll with CR Logo bug, 2005 May 11 (Box 101, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-279)
    - Consumer Reports Medical Guide.org B-Roll with CR Logo No bug, 2005 May 11 (Box 108, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0847)
    - Consumer Reports: Nearly Half of Americans Won't Get Flu Vaccine, Citing Long List of Poor Excuses Approximately 200,000 People Art Hospitalized Each Year from the Flu, Undated (Box 1, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-002)
    - Consumer Reports-Alar In Apples and Apple Juice, Undated (Box 26, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-032)
    - Consumer Repots Medical Guide, 2006 Feb. 07 (Box 101, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1126)
    - Consumer Union VNR: Bovine Growth Hormone - Milk, Undated (Box 69, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0209)
    - CR June Low-Carb Diet Food, 2004 Mar. 21 (Box 108, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0837)
    - CR Med Guide. Org, Undated (Box 99, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-400)
    - CRTV: Health Care Waste, 2001 (Box 82, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0183)
    - Dr. Beth Nash Consumer Reports Medical Guide.org, 2005 May 25 (Box 108, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-216)
    - Dr. Lipman: CR May '04 Cover Dangerous Supplements, 2004 Apr. 03 (Box 101, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1117)
    - Feeling Fine Show, 1982 Aug. 04 (Box 29, Video-reel RL11802-vid1-007)
    - Feeling Fine Show, 1982 Dec. 17 (Box 65, Video-reel RL11802-vid1-044)
    - Food Follies, Food Show, Undated (Box 84, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0493)
    - Food News & Views, 1993 Dec. 17 (Box 120, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0471)
    - Food Show, 1981 Oct. 26 (Box 46, Video-reel RL11802-vid1-026)
    - Food Show FB 21 #4 Reel #1, Undated (Box 13, Film-reel RL11802-F16-017)
    - Food Show FB 21 #4 Reel #2, Undated (Box 13, Film-reel RL11802-F16-018)
    - Health News and Notes, 2005 Sept. 01 (Box 99, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-399)
    - Health Week, 2001 Oct. 20 (Box 107, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0671)
    - Kim Kleman:, LH: Fast Foods, 2004 Aug. 10 (Box 108, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0836)
    - Kine 3 Diet Show, Undated (Box 33, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-036)
    - Medical Guide.org, 2005 May 09 (Box 108, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-204)
    - Medical Show, Undated (Box 12, Film-reel RL11802-F16-003)
    - Medicine Show, 1981 Oct. 26 (Box 47, Video-reel RL11802-vid1-023)
    - Mental Health Reports, 2004 Sept. 07 (Box 108, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-398)
    - Nancy Metcalf: CR June '05 Rating the Diets, 2005 May 10 (Box 101, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1143)
    - Nancy Metcalf: CR may 04 cover Dangerous Supplements, 2004 Apr. 29 (Box 101, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1125)
    - The Feeling Fine Show, 1982 Aug. 11 (Box 37, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-067)
    - The Feeling Fine Show, 1982 July 14 (Box 47, Video-reel RL11802-vid1-022)
    - The Feeling Fine Show, 1982 July 26 (Box 40, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-081)
    - The Feeling Fine Show, 1982 July 26 (Box 86, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-169)
    - The Feeling Fine Show, 1982 Sept. 13 (Box 16, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-014)
    - The Food Show, 1980 Feb. 07 (Box 84, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0497)
    - The Food Show, 1980 Sept. 23 (Box 15, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-025)
    - The Food Show, 1980 Sept. 23 (Box 86, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-178)
    - The Food Show, 1980 (Box 47, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-097)
    - The Food Show Reel 1, 1980 (Box 50, Film-reel RL11802-F16-159)
    - The Food Show Reel 2, 1980 (Box 50, Film-reel RL11802-F16-160)
    - The Medicine Show, 1980 (Box 54, Film-reel RL11802-F16-157)
    - The Medicine Show, 1980 (Box 57, Film-reel RL11802-F16-169)
    - The Medicine Show, 1980 (Box 37, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-060)
    - The Medicine Show, 1980 (Box 86, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-177)
    - The Medicine Show, 1980 May 29 (Box 15, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-019)
    - The Medicine Show FB 20-#24, Undated (Box 24, Film-reel RL11802-F16-119)
    - Warning: Dieting May be Hazardous to Your Healthy, 1989 Aug. 04 (Box 15, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-023)
    - Warning: Food May be Hazardous to Your Health, 1987 Aug. 21 (Box 38, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-050)
    - Warning: May be Hazardous to Your Health, 1985 Jan. 21 (Box 16, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-012)
    - Warning: May be Hazardous to Your Health, 1985 June 20 (Box 63, Video-reel RL11802-vid1-039)
    - Warning: Medicine May Be Hazardous to Your Health, 1988 Aug. 02 (Box 33, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-038)
    - Yonkers Tuna, 1992 Jan. 16 (Box 88, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-202)
  - Household, 1975-2004; undated; 13
    - 4-House Shows The All-Around-The-House-Show, Undated (Box 11, Film-reel RL11802-F16-006)
    - All Around the House Show, Undated (Box 10, Film-reel RL11802-F16-007)
    - All Around the House Show, Undated (Box 51, Film-reel RL11802-F16-161)
    - Checking Account #6, Undated (Box 33, Film-reel RL11802-F16-126)
    - Consumer Reports for TV Sales, 1975 Sept. (Box 17, Film-reel RL11802-F16-071)
    - Consumer Reports Guide to Baby Products, 1999 June 18 (Box 104, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0645)
    - Consumer Reports Last Minute Shopping, 2002 Dec. 18 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-222)
    - Consumer Reports Phone Hot Dog, Undated (Box 62, Film-reel RL11802-F16-175)
    - Consumer Reports: All Around the House, 1981 Oct. 26 (Box 62, Video-reel RL11802-vid1-036)
    - Full Program Dollar Signs: Mari McQueen on Home Improvements, 2004 Mar. 06 (Box 103, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1173)
    - The All Around the House Show, 1981 Feb. 05 (Box 34, Audio-cassette RL11802-Umatic-043)
    - The All Around the House Show, 1981 Feb. 05 (Box 86, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-170)
  - Television Series, 1986-2006; undated; 14
    - Consumer Reports, 1986 Jan. 10 (Box 39, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-045)
    - Consumer Reports, 1986 Jan. 10 (Box 39, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-046)
    - Consumer Reports, 1986 Jan. 10 (Box 59, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-124)
    - Consumer Reports, 1989 Feb. 23 (Box 16, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-003)
    - Consumer Reports, 1997 Sept. 05 (Box 27, Film-reel RL11802-F16-122)
    - Consumer Reports, 2000 Oct. 12 (Box 42, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0009)
    - Consumer Reports, Undated (Box 36, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-062)
    - Consumer Reports, Undated (Box 1, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-017)
    - Consumer Reports #10, Undated (Box 60, Video-reel RL11802-Vid1-033)
    - Consumer Reports #16, 1989 Mar. 21 (Box 63, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-148)
    - Consumer Reports #17 Creel VNR, 1989 Mar. 21 (Box 36, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-071)
    - Consumer reports #9, Undated (Box 33, Video-reel RL11802-vid1-008)
    - Consumer Reports (Bites), Undated (Box 100, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-239)
    - Consumer Reports Magazine, 1993 May 20 (Box 37, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-061)
    - Consumer Reports Magazine, 2005 Oct. 06 (Box 108, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-214)
    - Consumer Reports Magazine, 2005 Oct. 06 (Box 108, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-215)
    - Consumer Reports Magazine pts. 1 & 2, 1986 (Box 67, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-132)
    - Consumer Reports Presents #10, 1983 Aug. 04 (Box 38, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-051)
    - Consumer Reports Presents #10, 1983 Aug. 04 (Box 37, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-063)
    - Consumer Reports Presents #10, 1983 Aug. 09 (Box 26, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-033)
    - Consumer Reports Presents #10, 1985 June 21 (Box 43, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-113)
    - Consumer Reports Presents #9, 1985 June 19 (Box 15, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-018)
    - Consumer Reports Presents #9, 1985 June 19 (Box 87, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-185)
    - Consumer Reports Presents Show #10, 1983 July 26 (Box 28, Video-reel RL11802-vid1-004)
    - Consumer Reports Presents The Feeling Fine Show, 1982 Dec. 17 (Box 36, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-072)
    - Consumer Reports Presents the Smart Shopper Show, 1982 Dec. 22 (Box 62, Video-reel RL11802-vid1-038)
    - Consumer Reports Presents.. Show #10, 1983 July 29 (Box 86, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-175)
    - Consumer Reports Presents: The Car Show, 1981 Aug. 04 (Box 15, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-030)
    - Consumer Reports Presents: The Shop Around Show, 1981 Sept. 10 (Box 35, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-039)
    - Consumer Reports Shop smart B-Roll, 2005 Dec. 08 (Box 1, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-001)
    - Consumer Reports Smart Investment, 1987 (Box 85, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0367)
    - Consumer Reports Tag-VO #5, Undated (Box 16, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-005)
    - Consumer Reports Testing 3 of 4, Undated (Box 34, Film-reel RL11802-F16-132)
    - Consumer Reports: Best of Consumer Reports, 1981 Oct. 26 (Box 63, Video-reel RL11802-vid1-040)
    - Consumer Reports: Houses and Condos, 1986 (Box 85, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0366)
    - Shop Smart Launch Issue EPK - B-Roll and Soundbites, 2006 July 26 (Box 1, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-015)
    - Shop Smart Launch Issue EPK - B-Roll and Soundbites Embargoes for Release, 2006 Aug. 01 (Box 101, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-276)
  - Youth Programming, 1982-2003; undated; 15
    - Buy Me That 3: A Kid's Guide to Food Advertising, 1992 (Box 138, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-728)
    - Buy Me That 3: Kids Guide to Food Advertising, 1994 Aug. 25 (Box 39, Video-reel RL11802-vid1-012)
    - Buy Me That Too! A Kid's Survival Guide to TV Advertising, 1991 (Box 138, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-727)
    - Buy Me That! A Kids' Survival Guide to T.V. Advertising, 1989 Nov. 15 (Box 36, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-070)
    - Buy Me That! A Kids' Survival Guide to Advertising, 1990 July 16 (Box 16, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-015)
    - Buy Me That! A Kids' Survival Guide to T.V. Advertising, 1990 Jan. 09 (Box 39, Video-reel RL11802-vid1-010)
    - Buy Me That! A Kids' Survival Guide to TV Advertising, 1989 Nov. 15 (Box 15, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-024)
    - Buy Me That! A Kids' Survival Guide to TV Advertising, 1992 Feb. 14 (Box 15, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-022)
    - Buy Me That! A Kid's Survival Guide to TV Advertising, 1989 (Box 138, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-726)
    - Captive Kids, 1995 Apr. 18 (Box 83, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0467)
    - Captive Kids: Commercial Pressures on Kids at Schools, TRT 10:15, 1995 (Box 138, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-294)
    - Consumer Reports The Not for Kids Only, 1982 May 04 (Box 65, Video-reel RL11802-vid1-041)
    - Consumer Reports: The Not For Kids Only Show, 1987 May 20 (Box 34, Audio-cassette RL11802-Umatic-044)
    - CRTV Stories Based on Zillions, Undated (Box 82, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0182)
    - CRTV Zillions Stories, Undated (Box 82, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0181)
    - Earth to Kids: A Guide to Products for a Healthy Planet, 1990 Nov. 26 (Box 33, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-037)
    - Kids Talk About Advertising, 1990 July 10 (Box 88, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-206)
    - Not for Kids Only, Undated (Box 39, Video-reel RL11802-vid1-011)
    - Penny Power, 1985 (Box 37, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-065)
    - Penny Power, 1985 June 17 (Box 15, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-017)
    - Penny Power, 1985 June 20 (Box 47, Video-reel RL11802-vid1-021)
    - Selling America's Kids, 1990 July 17 (Box 88, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-205)
    - Selling America's Kids, 1990 July 17 (Box 88, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-209)
    - Tricks of the Trade Kids Rule, 2003 Apr. 01 (Box 103, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1188)
    - WABC Captive Kids, 1995 Apr. 18 (Box 84, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0494)
    - Zap Awards, Undated (Box 84, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-129)
    - Zillions Magazine Zap Awards B-Roll: Kids Expose Bad Ads, Undated (Box 84, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-128)
    - Zillions Magazine Zap Awards B-Roll: Kids Expose Bad Ads, Undated (Box 84, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-130)
    - Zillions on Our Home, 1995 Mar. 07 (Box 82, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0160)
    - Zillions TV, 1993 Aug. 28 (Box 83, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0451)
    - Zillions TV, 1993 Nov. 01 (Box 88, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-197)
    - Zillions TV, 1993 Nov. 23 (Box 45, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-106)
    - Zillions TV, 1993 Oct. 09 (Box 40, Video-reel RL11802-Vid2-003)
    - Zillions TV, Undated (Box 83, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0449)
    - Zillions TV, Undated (Box 83, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0450)
    - Zillions TV #14, Undated (Box 42, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-090)
    - Zillions TV Rough Cut Running Order 2, 1993 Aug. 28 (Box 66, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0141)
    - Zillions TV Spanish Version, 1994 Jan. 03 (Box 88, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-196)
    - Zillions TV Spanish Version, 1994 Jan. 03 (Box 88, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-208)
    - Zillions TV Spanish Version, 1994 Jan. 03 (Box 82, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0164)
  - Other Video, 1970-2006; undated; 16
    - Cass #14, 1985 Dec. 14 (Box 60, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-127)
    - Cass #15, 1985 Dec. 13 (Box 42, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-084)
    - Cass #16, 1985 Dec. 13 (Box 45, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-101)
    - Cass #17, 1985 Dec. 13 (Box 40, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-080)
    - Cass #18, 1985 Dec. 13 (Box 43, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-119)
    - Cass #19 CU, 1985 Dec. 13 (Box 64, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-144)
    - Cass #20 CU, 1985 Dec. 13 (Box 64, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-146)
    - Cass #40, 1986 Mar. 04 (Box 60, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-126)
    - Cass #41, 1986 Mar. 04 (Box 42, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-088)
    - Cass #42, 1986 Mar. 04 (Box 43, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-111)
    - Cass #43, 1986 Mar. 04 (Box 45, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-102)
    - Cass #44 Consumers Unions, 1986 Mar. 04 (Box 64, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-145)
    - Cass #45 Consumer Union, 1986 Mar. 04 (Box 35, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-040)
    - Cass #46, 1986 Mar. 04 (Box 60, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-129)
    - Consumer Reports 1936-1980 Roll #1, Undated (Box 120, Film-reel RL11802-F16-203)
    - Consumer Reports 1936-1980 Roll #2, Undated (Box 120, Film-reel RL11802-F16-205)
    - Consumer Reports 1936-1980 Roll #3, Undated (Box 120, Film-reel RL11802-F16-204)
    - Consumer Union Roll 10, 1985 Nov. 22 (Box 43, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-110)
    - Consumer Union Roll 11, 1985 Nov. 22 (Box 42, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-085)
    - Consumer Union Roll 12, 1985 Nov. 22 (Box 42, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-087)
    - Consumer Union Roll 13, 1985 Nov. 22 (Box 43, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-109)